<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Purpose on Becoming Inspirational</title>
    <link>http://becominginspirational.com/categories/purpose/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Purpose on Becoming Inspirational</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2017 22:55:46 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://becominginspirational.com/categories/purpose/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Inspiration in My About Page</title>
      <link>http://becominginspirational.com/post/inspiring-people-in-my-about-page/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2017 22:55:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://becominginspirational.com/post/inspiring-people-in-my-about-page/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;My main goal in the about page of this blog is to inspire people to take action. Here I will discuss how I actually provoke this inspiration into my readers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-I claim to know what I&amp;rsquo;m doing.- If you look at the about page of my website and feel inspired, then I&amp;rsquo;m on the right track. You might be inspired to look further into my blog, or just inspired to &lt;strong&gt;take action&lt;/strong&gt; of some sort. That action could be inspiring others to become more inspirational by sharing the page. -As I mention in my about page. I will explain tactics in my about page that I believe to be inspirational. Consider this a meta page if you must. -&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;building-professional-expertise-and-trust:33ac8f2327bc1d95ad55331c9b10557d&#34;&gt;Building Professional Expertise and Trust&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To start with, I explain what inspiration is and give myself professional expertise/trustworthiness by defining inspiration and giving proof that I know what I&amp;rsquo;m doing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;building-up-connections-with-readers:33ac8f2327bc1d95ad55331c9b10557d&#34;&gt;Building Up Connections With Readers&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I believe it is much easier to inspire someone I know and trust than it is to inspire some random person on the internet. Therefore, a big part of inspiring my readers is trying to build connections with my readers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;clear-specific-purpose:33ac8f2327bc1d95ad55331c9b10557d&#34;&gt;Clear, Specific Purpose&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then I move on to explaining why inspiration runs the world and give an example of how inspiration changes peoples lives. I give many reasons why inspiration is such a motivating factor to putting meaning and finding reasons to complete tasks. I make inspiration sound like this huge cloud of awesomeness that will make your life a much happier life. I&amp;rsquo;m not lying when I say this, but I&amp;rsquo;m using to help inspire you to &lt;strong&gt;take action&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;inspiration-as-the-solution-to-all-your-problems:33ac8f2327bc1d95ad55331c9b10557d&#34;&gt;Inspiration as the Solution to All Your Problems&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I explain inspiration as the tool to overcoming fears and breaking willpower. I bet many people out their feel inspired to do things on a daily basis. However, most will always end up looking back down at their phones or looking on in their youtube feed when they feel inspired, this gets rid of the creative ability when feeling inspired. I use this commonality in today&amp;rsquo;s society to reach out to everyone having these occurring problems. I build this &lt;strong&gt;personal connection&lt;/strong&gt; with readers that makes them feel like they relate to me and others in this way and I give them a solution to it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I make inspiration the answer to all modern day problems. I claim that with enough inspiration anyone can overcome their fears, break into the wall that stops them from asking that girl out, to simply achieving a happy life. I claim that inspiration allows them to do anything they set their mind to, in a creative and fun way. Not a demanding and hard way. I truly believe in these claims, which adds genuine connections with my readers which builds the inspiration in them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I could go into how I provoke inspiration in this article as well. However, I think you get the point. Inspiration can be done in many differnet ways. Communication is very influential to being inspired and must be relied on in almost all interactions with other people. Nature can also be an inspiration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;benefits-to-being-inspirational:33ac8f2327bc1d95ad55331c9b10557d&#34;&gt;Benefits to Being Inspirational&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I give people many benefits to being inspirational. From building connections and communities to further our knowledge and educational efforts.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>